(一年前)
如果事情按我们预想的方向发展
This thing goes our way
我要跳进那个笼子里
And I...Triple lindy into that box...
你知道我是有去无回吧
...You know I'm not coming back.
你得发誓不会试着救我回来
You got to promise not to try to bring me back.
去找莉莎
You go find Lisa.
你要过正常且简单有序的生活  迪恩
You go live some normal, apple-pie life.
答应我  迪恩
Promise me, Dean.
答应我
Promise me.
(如今)
还好吧
You okay?
当然  很好
Yeah, I'm good.
[邪恶力量 第6季第1集]
幸亏这是在非死不可出现前  不是吗
And thank god this is before facebook, right?
否则我和我那只山羊肯定得
Because it'd be me and that goat...
红透整个因特网
...All over the internet.
-没错  -所以
- That's right. - So...
别误会  好吗  别抱怨
Don't get me wrong, right? No complaints.
但如果你现在对我说
But if you'd have said to me,
嘿  你  十五年之后
"Hey, you -- 15 years from now?
就郊区养老去吧
Suburbia."
-噢  是的  -了解吗
- Oh. Yeah. - Right?
相信我  深有体会
Believe me, I know.
你曾经周游了很多地方咯
So, you've traveled around a lot, huh?
没错  几乎前半辈子都在
Yeah, my whole life, pretty much.
然后呢
And?
不知道该说啥了
I don't know.
行了
Come on.
你  是什么时候搬来的  一年前吧
You -- what, you moved in, what, about a year ago?
是的  差不多
Yeah, thereabouts.
既然我请你喝了一年的啤酒了
So I been buying you beer for a year.
你是不是也该回馈我些惊险刺激的细节呢
And I think that means you owe me a couple of gory details.
不  其实没什么好讲的  不是吗
Oh, no. There's not much to tell, you know?
也就是  嗯
It's, uh...
我到处周游
I lived on the road...
找一些  没人愿意做的活儿干干
Took, uh, crap jobs that nobody else wanted.
-比如呢  -比如说
- Like? - Like...
在虫害防治中心干干
Pest control.
真的吗
Really?
虫害防治中心
Pest control.
是的
Yeah.
有个搭档和你一起工作
You get to work with a partner.
你可以  帮助民众
You get to... Help people.
你根本无法想象有些人家的墙里都有些什么
You have no idea what's in some people's walls.
那些能把他们给生吞活剥了
It could eat 'em alive.
哇哦
Yeesh.
当然  那都是过去了  而现在
'course, that was then. And now...
你确实挺值得尊敬的
You're practically respectable.
是啊
Yeah. Wow.
我想是吧
I guess so.
确切地说  应该是吓人吧
That's kind of scary, actually.
谢了  伙计们
Thanks, guys.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我想她喜欢你
I think she likes you.
你确定
You think?
(女服务生名字和电话)
你怎么回事儿啊
What is it with you?!
似乎  每次都这样
Like, every time!
妞儿总喜欢挖人墙角吧
It's like chicks specifically dig unavailable guys.
谁知道啊
who knew?
好了
Okay.
-明天见  -明天见
- I will see you tomorrow. - I'll see you tomorrow.
谢谢招待了  伙计
Thanks, man.
没人打电话找失踪的人吗
And no one's called about a missing person?
(911紧急呼叫情况)
不  很有可能就是今天
No, this would have been today.
就是说温兰和欧克街那里没有任何上报吗
So no reports of anything around Vineland and Oak street,
在改造的那个旅馆附近也没有吗
near that hotel renovation?
算是直觉吧
Uh, call it a hunch.
我当警察很多年了
I've been a cop for a long time.
好了  是的  不  我明天打给你吧
Okay, yeah. No, I'll call you tomorrow.
你也是  伙计  再见
You too, man. Bye.
嘿
Hey.
谁啊
Who was that?
西德  我刚约了打扑克牌
Sid. I'm just setting up a poker game.
在晚上十一点半
11:30.
这么晚了么
Is it really?
难怪我打给他时他说自己都睡下了
Well, that explains why he was asleep when I called.
我马上就来
I'll be right up.
好的
Okay.
迪恩  那是枪吗
Dean! Is that a gun?
不  不  是的
No, no. Yeah.
那个  我有许可证
Well, it's -- I got a permit for it.
你拿枪就为了射格利克曼的狗吗
What, to shoot the Glickmans' dog?
我以为是只负鼠
I thought that was a possum.
记得我说过我在虫害防治中心工作过吗
Remember when I said I was in pest control?
负鼠可能携带狂犬病毒  所以
Well, possums carry rabies, so...
我还真不知道
I did not know that.
是啊  是啊  负鼠
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Possums --
负鼠会害出人命的  西德
Possums kill, Sid.
见鬼
Oh, crap.
怎么了
What's that?
硫磺
Sulfur.
-我得走了  -等等  迪恩
- I got to go.  - Hold on, dean!
搞什么鬼
What the hell?
我只是在找锤子
Just getting a hammer.
我刚刚碰见西德了
So, I just ran into Sid.
你是不是差点把那只约克夏犬射死
Did you almost shoot a yorkie?
差不多
Technically.
怎么回事
What's going on?
没什么
Nothing.
我不相信
How come I don't believe you?
我  我就是
I just -- I, uh, I-I got this --
我也不知道  最近有点疑神疑鬼的
I don't know, spidey sense.
好吧
Okay.
你是在猎魔吗
Are you hunting something?
老实讲
Honestly?
一开始我以为是的
Uh, at first, I thought that I was.
但其实是我瞎紧张了
But I'm pretty sure that I got worked up over nothing.
我...
It's, uh, you know...
我有时会这样
It happens.
你确定没事吗
Are you sure?
不如这样
I'll tell you what --
我有猎魔强迫症
Just because, you know, I have an ocd thing about this,
不如你和本一起去看看电影
why don't, uh, why don't you and Ben go to the movies,
去芝士蛋糕工厂吃点东西
hit the cheesecake factory --
和大伙出去玩玩
You know, hang out with the teeming masses,
我再最后检查一次  确保万无一失
and I'll do one last sweep just to be 100%.
好吧
Okay.
小心点
Be careful.
我一直很小心
Careful's my middle name.
你好啊  迪恩
Hiya, dean.
看看天启带来的后果
Look what the apocalypse shook loose.
追踪我留下的线索好玩吗
You have fun sniffing that trail?
我可是很享受牵着你鼻子走的感觉
'cause I sure had fun patting you around.
你不可能还...
You can't be...
我当然可以
Oh, sure I can!
-不可能  -可以的  臭小子
- No.  - Yeah, kiddo.
上帝把你的好兄弟卡西救回来了  对吗
The big daddy brought your pal Cass back, right?
为什么我就不能被救回来呢
So why not me?
给你们美好的生活增添点乐趣
Add a little spice to all that -- that sugar.
玩真的吗
Really?
我们共同经历了这么多事情
After all we've been through together?
你的小日子过的很舒服嘛
You know, you got a great little life here.
美女老婆  那么理解你
Pretty lady -- real understanding.
还有个不错的小孩
Hell of a kid.
你是怎么把草坪理得那么整齐的
And how do you keep your lawn so green?
拜托  迪恩
I mean, come on, Dean.
虽然我知道你不怎么聪明
You never been what I'd call brainy,
但你真的傻到以为
But did you really think
你的小日子可以继续这么过下去吗
you were gonna get to keep all of this?
你得知道我们早晚会找上门儿的  老兄
You had to know that we were coming for you sometime, pal.
你逃避不了过去的
You can't outrun your past.
你好  迪恩
Hey, Dean.
我还指望你...
I was expecting, uh...
给我来个拥抱
I don't know, a hug,
或者朝我泼点圣水呢
some holy water in the face -- something.
我死了吗
So I'm dead?
这里是天堂吗
This is heaven?
黄眼恶魔杀了我  然后
Yellow eyes killed me, and now --
黄眼恶魔  你见到了他吗
Yellow eyes? That's what you saw?
什么叫见到
"Saw"?
你被下毒了
You were poisoned.
所以不管你以为
So whatever kind of crazy
你见到了什么  都是假的
crap you think you been seeing, it's not real.
那么  你是真实的吗
So, then, are you...Real?
-还是我...  -我是真实的
- Or am I still -  - I'm real.
我证明给你看
Here, let me save you the trouble.
我就是我
All me.
可算弄完了
That's nasty.
小萨姆
Sammy?
是的
Yeah.
是我
It's me.
等等  等等
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
你你  你跳进去了  兄弟
You -- you -- you were -- you were gone, man.
我说  就是那样
I mean, that -- that was it.
-你到底是怎么  -我也不知道
- How the hell are you --  - I don't know.
你说你不知道是什么意思
What do you mean you don't know?
就是  没有头绪
I mean, no idea.
我就是回来了
I-I'm just back.
是上帝  还是  卡西
Well, was it god, or -- or -- or Cass?
卡西知道这事吗
I mean, does Cass know anything about it?
你说呢  我一直在召唤他
You tell me. I've been calling.
他还没回应我的祈祷
Cass hasn't answered my prayers.
我甚至不知道他在哪里
I don't even know where he is.
我  在下面
I mean, I was... Down there,
接着  几分钟后  开始下雨了
and then, next minute, it's raining,
我发现自己独自躺在那里
and I'm lying in that field, alone.
毫无无头绪的寻找是谁救了我
It's kind of hard to go looking for whatever saved you
这有点难
when you got no leads.
但我找过了
But I looked.
相信我  我试过了
I mean, believe me, I looked...
找了好几周
for weeks.
等等  好几周
Wait, weeks?
你回来多久了
How long you been back?
你回来多久了  萨姆
How long you been back, Sam?
一年左右
About a year.
-一年了  -迪恩
- About a year?  - Dean --
这一整年来你都在这个世上
You been back practically this whole time?!
你该死的失去了发消息的能力了吗
What, did you lose the ability to send a friggin' text message?!
你终于得到梦寐以求的东西了  迪恩
You finally had what you wanted, Dean.
-我想要我的弟弟活着  -你想要个家庭
- I wanted my brother, alive.  - You wanted a family.
你想了很久了  一直以来都想  我了解你
You have for a long time, maybe the whole time. I know you.
因为我们生存的方式你才放弃了这个想法
You only gave it up because of the way we lived.
但你拥有了常人的生活  建立了家庭
But you had something, and you were building something.
如果我就这么出现了  迪恩
Had I shown up, Dean,
你就会离开这种生活
you would have just run off.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
但这感觉就像  一切过后
But it felt like after everything,
你应该过上正常人的生活
you deserved some regular life.
那你都在做些什么
What have you been doing?
猎魔抓鬼
Hunting.
你把我甩开  自己单干吗
You left me alone, and you were flying solo?
不是单干
Not solo.
-什么  -我和一些朋友一起
- What?  - I hooked up with some other people.
你竟然和陌生人共事
You? Working with strangers?
他们更像是家人
They're more like family.
他们就在这里
And they're here.
你好
Hi.
天哪  对于猎魔人来说  你的脸真是精致
My god, you have delicate features for a hunter.
什么
Excuse me?
迪恩  这位是格温·坎贝尔
Dean, Gwen Campbell.
终于见到你了  萨姆经常提起你
Good to finally meet you. Sam's gone on and on.
这位是克里斯蒂安
And this is Christian...
还有马克
...and Mark.
坎贝尔
Campbell.
你好
Hi.
坎  坎贝尔  像
Cam-- Campbell? Like...
是你们母亲的姓
Like your mom.
他们是第三代的堂表兄妹
They're cousin. Third cousin.
更远的远房亲戚
Something, something twice removed.
他们的成长经历  跟妈妈和我们一样
They grew up in the life, like mom and like us.
我以为妈妈的亲戚都没了
I thought all of mom's relatives were gone.
我很抱歉
And I'm sorry.
只是  为什么我一个都不认识
It's just, you know, why didn't we know about any of you?
他们也不认识你
'cause they didn't know about you.
但现在我让你们团聚了
Not until I brought you all together.
萨穆埃尔
Samuel?
来抱抱
Come here.
我是你外公
I'm your grandfather.
孩子们  给我点时间和我外孙独处  谢谢
Guys, give me a second with my grandsons here, please.
今天你见到了好多死而复生的人
Lot of resurrections in your face today.
没事  花一分钟接受事实
It's all right. Take a minute.
肯定要比一分钟久
It's gonna take a little more than a minute.
到底怎么回事
I mean, what the hell?
这  这是怎么发生的
H-how did this happen?
我们猜想救了萨姆的东西复活了我
We're guessing whatever pulled Sam up pulled me down.
不管它是什么  我们都成了它的一部分
So, whatever this is, we're both a part of it.
但你们还不知道它是什么
But you don't know what that is.
没错
Bingo.
你们没有线索  一头雾水是吗
And you have no leads? Nothing?
这  这真是
Well, this -- this is, uh...
不会再有复活者从那扇门走出来了吧
No more doornails coming out of that door, is there?
就我们所知  只有萨穆埃尔  和我
As far as we know, it's Samuel, and it's me.
所以我是这里唯一一个
Okay, am I the only one here
觉得这不太对劲吗
that thinks that this can't all just be fine?
相信我  没事的
Believe me, you're not.
我也很想去找你
I wanted to come get you, of course.
只是萨姆执意不肯把你牵扯进来
Sam was adamant about leaving you out,
所以我们尊重他的意见
so we did.
直到这事发生
Until this.
嗯
Right.
可你们怎么会跑到我车库里去的
So, then you ended up in my garage how?
在你被袭击的前几天  我也被袭了
I got hit before you did, few days ago.
它们给我下毒
Dosed up with poison.
-谁下的毒  -灯灵
- By? - Couple of djinn.
灯灵
Djinn?
我一直以为它们常年隐居洞穴
I thought those were -- were cave-dwelling hermit-type.
特立独行
That's pretty exotic.
看来它们的习性变了
Not anymore, at least.
他们和普通人没什么两样
These...look like regular people.
能轻松融入人类的世界
They can blend in.
哪怕与你轻微碰触  就能叫你一命呜呼
And all they got to do to kill you is touch you.
其毒液一旦侵入你体内
Their toxins get in your system,
不多时  便会使你产生幻觉
all of a sudden you're hallucinating
令噩梦时时闪现
your worst nightmares,
没多久  你就会踏上黄泉路了
and pretty soon you O.D.
那为什么你现在安然无恙
Well, then how are you breathing air?
萨穆埃尔找到了解药
Samuel had a cure.
你有办法解灯灵的毒
You got a cure for djinn poison?
略知一二
I know a few things.
有空我教你
Stick around, I'll show you tricks
这可是你老爸毕生梦寐以求的本事
your daddy never even dreamed of.
为什么这东西会盯上我们
Okay, why are these things after us?
以前我们干掉过他们的同伙
Well, you did stake one a while back.
它们找上我之后
After they came after me,
我们敢肯定
we were pretty certain that
它们也一定不会放过你
they were gonna go gunning for you next.
莉莎和本  这会应该到家了
Lisa and Ben -- they're at the house right now.
-要是那东西现在找上门来  -别担心
- If that thing comes back - It's all right.
我找人在那边看着他们呢
I already sent someone over there to watch 'em.
你现在赶紧送我回家
You got to take me home right now.
莉莎
Lisa?!
莉莎  本
Lisa! Ben?!
本
Ben!
你们到底跑哪儿去了
Where the hell have you been?
我们去看电影了  有跟你说过的啊
We -- we were at the movies. You knew that.
迪恩
Dean.
发生什么事了吗
What happened?
-你们快上楼收拾东西  -我们要去哪
- Go upstairs and pack a bag. - Where are we going?
我一个老友家  快去
I'm taking us to a friend's house. Go.
别担心  你先上去  我就来
It's okay. Go on up. I'll be there in a sec.
老天啊
Oh, my god.
莉莎  本  不知道你们还记不记得
Lisa, Ben, I don't know if you remember --
萨姆
Sam.
靠
Damn it.
很高兴见到你  鲍比  好久不见
It's good to see you, too, Bobby. It's been a while.
你来一定有大事
If you're here, something's wrong.
鲍比  这是莉莎和本
Bobby, this is Lisa and Ben.
终于还是见面了
Well, it's nice to finally meet you two.
把这儿当自己家吧
Mi casa es su casa.
你们上楼歇歇吧
Maybe you want to just go upstairs.
电视坏了  不过我这读者文摘倒有不少
Tv's broken, but there's plenty of Reader's Digest.
屋里的东西别乱碰
Just don't touch the decor, okay?
假装是一碰就走火了
Assume it's all loaded.
鲍比  你好啊
Hey, Bobby.
萨姆
Sam.
这事你知道
You knew?
你知道萨姆没死
You knew Sam was alive.
是的
Yeah.
你知道多久了
How long?
-听着  -多久了
- Look - How long?!
一年了
All year.
你开玩笑呢吧
You got to be kidding me.
时光倒流我仍旧会这么做
And I'd do it again.
-为什么  -因为你退出江湖了  迪恩
- Why?! - Because you got out, Dean!
你离开了这种生活
You walked away from the life.
我他妈的有多高兴
And I was so damn grateful,
你根本就不明白
You got no idea.
你知道抛下一切于我意味着什么吗
Do you have any clue what walking away meant for me?
当然知道  回到老婆孩子身边
Yeah -- a woman and a kid
不再为英年早逝而惴惴不安
and not getting your guts ripped out at age 30.
那就意味着这一切
That's what it meant.
老婆孩子
That woman and that kid
是因为你求我  才去找的
-- I went to them because you asked me to.
-很好  -对谁有好处
- Good. - Good for who?
我当时满脑子悲伤快逆流成河了
I showed up on their doorstep
就那样莫名其妙出现在他们家门口
half out of my head with grief.
天知道她俩怎么会让我进去
God knows why they even let me in.
我夜夜买醉  噩梦连连
I drank too much. I had nightmares.
走街串巷  收集了上千本书
I looked everywhere. I collected hundreds of books,
千方百计想把你救出来
Trying to find anything to bust you out.
你说过不会再管的
You promised you'd leave it alone.
我怎么可能不管
Of course I didn't leave it alone!
报警抓我啊
Sue me!
一整年
A damn year?
你眼睁睁看我深陷痛苦的泥沼却不来拉我
You couldn't put me out of my misery?
听着  我知道一切都很难接受
Look, I get it wasn't easy.
但这就是生活
But that's life!
这就是猎魔人
And it's as close to happiness
永远无法得到的幸福生活
as I've ever seen a hunter get.
孩子  骗你非我本意
It ain't like I wanted to lie to you, son.
但是你已经隐退了
But you were out, Dean.
我看起来像退出了吗
Do I look out to you?
他还好吧
How's he doing?
没事  你呢
He's okay. How are you?
鲍比是有点古里古怪的  但他是个好人
Look, I know Bobby's a little crotchety, but he's great.
他会好好照顾你们
He's gonna look after you guys.
我和萨姆要走了
Me and Sam, we're gonna head out.
去多久
For how long?
莉莎  对不起
I'm so sorry, Lisa.
对不起什么
For what?
这些事情都是冲着我来的
Those things were coming for me.
我早该知道的
And I should've known.
恶魔的踪迹又岂是你能预料的
How could you know a monster was gonna show up?
我早该知道的
I should've known.
我早该知道如果和你在一起
I should've known that if I stayed with you
它们就会跟来
That something would come,
这是它们一贯的行事风格
because something always does.
我太傻太鲁莽了
But I was stupid and reckless and...
过去的一切刻骨铭心
You can't outrun your past.
你是来道别的吗
You're saying goodbye.
我是来道歉的
I'm saying I'm sorry...
为一切的一切
For everything.
一切
Everything.
你真是个笨蛋
You're an idiot.
虽然我们的生活不够完美
I mean, I know it wasn't greeting-card perfect,
但是至少我们在一起
But we were in it together.
我几乎是个废人
I was a wreck half the time.
那个拯救了世界的人
Yeah, well, the guy that basically just saved the world
突然出现在你门前
shows up at your door,
你希望他是有事而来
you expect him to have a couple of issues.
你和本一直都相处融洽
And you're always so amazing with Ben.
你知道我需要什么  我只是需要
You know what I wanted, more than anything...
一个
was...
本能够崇拜的对象
...a guy that Ben could look up to...
就像
...like...
就像一个父亲
like a dad.
迪恩  你觉得这样不好吗
So, you're saying it's all bad, Dean?
可是这一年是我一生中最美好的日子
'cause it was the best year of my life.
有什么安排
What's the plan?
现在先备好货  准备起来
Well, right now, we stock up, get set.
你的意思是  没安排
So you're saying there is no plan.
我们从长计议
We'll find 'em.
耐心一点
Just got to be patient.
嗯  好吧
Yeah, okay.
我有个建议
Oh, here's an alt.
我们干嘛不直接去干掉那些
Why don't we go kill the sons of bitches
闯进我家里的混蛋
that broke into my home?
迪恩  冷静点  我们会处理的
Relax, Dean. We got it handled.
灯灵很难对付
Djinn are hard to draw out.
你有一段时间没接触这些了
Now, you've been out of the game for a while.
交给专家吧
Leave it to the professionals.
好  没问题
Yeah. Sure.
小小的建议
Tiny suggestion.
设个诱饵  灯灵会好对付些
You see, djinn are easier to draw out when you got bait.
他们想要的是萨姆和我
They want Sam and me.
他们知道我住在哪里
They know where I live.
我已经很久都没猎魔了
Now, I haven't been hunting in a while,
这次准备豁出去了
But I'm gonna stick my neck out
去我家吧  再适合不过来
and guess that's a pretty good place for us to go.
瞧  我还是挺专业的吧
See? It's almost like I'm a professional.
我喜欢这个
I love this one.
你的还是你老婆的
Yours or, uh, your wife's?
帮个忙  别碰这个
Do me a favor -- don't touch that.
高尔夫
Golf?
你不是吧
Really?
就是  就是运动运动啊
It's a -- it's a sport.
房子不错啊
Nice house.
好啦  我是辣妈行了吧  随你埋汰
Oh, yeah. Go ahead, say it -- call me a soccer mom.Whatever.
"辣妈"
"Soccer mom," Huh?
我得去内联网上查查这词
Well, I'll have to look that up on the "Intranet."
不管你信不信  我...
You know, believe it or not, I...
我懂  迪恩
I get it, Dean.
你想过普通人的生活
You wanted a normal life.
你母亲曾经也这么想
Your mom wanted a normal life, too.
你的人生观
You remind me of her, actually.
让我情不自禁想起了她
The attitude, for one thing.
你弟弟告诉你
Your brother tell you what
过去几个月我们一直在对付什么了吗
we've been dealing with the past few months?
还没
No, not really.
我从没见过类似的东西
I've never seen anything quite like it.
日夜不停地搞破坏
Been working 'round the clock.
-那到底是什么  -我们不清楚
- So what's going on?  - We don't know.
无论是什么
But whatever it is,
它远超过几个灯灵一起作怪
it goes way past a couple of djinn acting off --
就像夜行怪在白天攻击
Nocturnals attacking in broad daylight,
狼人在月缺之夜活动
Werewolves out on the half-moon,
这种生物我们闻所未闻
creatures that we've never even seen before.
我们根本不清楚它们是什么
We don't...we don't even know what they are.
我见到很多被吃了一半的人类心脏
I'm knee-deep in half-eaten human hearts
还有被吸干血的十岁孩童
and exsanguinated 10-year-olds,
这一切令我
and it's all making me...
惶恐不安
uneasy.
你觉得是什么
So what's your theory?
你来告诉我
You tell me.
我们只知道它正蓄势待发
All we really know is it's all hands on deck.
现在我们只能互相扶持了
We're counting on each other right now.
坎贝尔家族的命运也在此一搏了
That's how it is with Campbells.
迪恩  我们需要你
We need you, Dean.
我明白  但是...
Look, I hear you, but...
迪恩  你是家族的一份子
You don't know what you're part of, Dean.
你的祖辈在"五月花"号上取下了
You know, you had ancestors hacking the heads off vamps
吸血鬼的首级
on the Mayflower.
我要说的是我们血脉相连
What I'm saying is that we're your blood.
当我们面对死亡威胁
And we're out there dying,
尝试去阻止未知的怪物
trying to get in front of whatever this is.
也许现在不是打高尔夫的最好时机
Maybe not the best time for golf.
你好像不太爱说话
You don't really say much, do you?
沉默是金
Enough.
有它们活动的迹象吗
Any sign of 'em?
树丛中有三个灯灵
Three djinn off in the trees.
那些灯灵坐在那里盯着我们
Those djinn are just sitting out there, watching us.
-大家都走吧  -什么
- Everybody's got to clear out.  - What?
除非我和萨姆落单  否则他们不会来
They're not gonna come in here until me and Sam are alone.
你是要我们抛下你们  孤立无援吗
So, what, I'm supposed to leave you here with no backup?
迪恩说的对
Dean's right.
他们很聪明  不等人数占优是绝不动手
They're smart. They'd wait till they weren't outnumbered.
好吧  我们不会走远
All right, we won't be far.
他们一来就打电话给我们  听到了吗
You call when they come, you hear?
没问题
You bet.
好的  收拾东西  准备离开
All right, pack up. We're out of here.
你还好吧
You okay?
还好
Oh, yeah.
不  这...
Yeah. No, this is...
这太疯狂了
This is crazy.
我是说  你  外公
I mean, you, grandpa.
不管是谁让你们起死回生
Whoever brought you back...
-他们不想被发现  -我知道
- They don't want to be found.  - Yeah, I get that.
但他们是谁  想要什么  又为了什么
But who are they, and what do they...what do they want? Why?
我也想知道
That's a good question.
你还记得吗
Do you remember it?
什么
What?
-那个笼子  -记得
- The cage. - Yeah.
-你想要  -不是
- You want to... - No.
如果这事和谁有关
Well, if anybody can relate...
迪恩  我不想谈这事了  我回来了
Dean, I don't want to talk about it. I'm back.
我可以呼吸到新鲜空气  喝上啤酒
I get to breathe fresh air, h-have a beer,
全家一同猎魔  并与你重逢
hunt with my family, see you again.
我又何必去想地狱里的事呢
So why exactly would I want to think about hell?
你真的认为...
And you really think...
迪恩  他们已经死了  你知道的
Dean, they're already dead, and you know it.
这一切因我而起
This is happening because of me!
迪恩
Dean!
西德
Sid.
上次你逃过一劫
You made it through that last trip,
要不这次来份巨无霸补回来吧
So how about a big, fat double dose?
坏消息是它会杀了你
Bad news...it'll kill you.
好消息就是
The good news?
至少你会死个痛快
At least you'll go fast.
这是为我们父亲报仇  你这狗日的
That's for our father, you son of a bitch.
我  我在那屋子里睡不着
I just -- I-I couldn't sleep at that house.
没事  别担心  一会给迪恩打电话
It's okay. Don't worry. We'll call Dean.
别担心他们  迪恩
Ah, don't worry about them, Dean.
看我的吧
Worry about me.
不
No!
好了好了  孩子
There, there, kiddo.
离他远点
You stay away from him!
莉莎
Lisa!
-喝下去吧  -本  不要
- Drink it. - Ben, no!
你会感觉好些的
You'll feel better.
不
No!
都是你的错
It's all your fault.
莉莎
Lisa!
这  这东西
This, something else --
我们都知道这是什么
we both know that's details.
日后他必会受到这个的影响
There's something's coming for this one,
你是无法阻止的
and you can't stop it.
都是你的错
It's all your fault.
-莉莎  -喝了它
- Lisa! - Drink it.
你会感觉好些的
You'll feel better.
-本  别喝  -你的错
- Ben, don't! - Your fault.
你阻止不了的
Can't stop it.
不
No!
我来对付她  你去帮迪恩
I got her. Go get Dean.
-抓住她了  -放轻松  宝贝
- Got her. - Relax, hon.
我们不会杀你的
We're not gonna kill you.
快点  在他们回来前  把她塞进货车里
Get her in the van. Quick, now, before the boys get back.
萨穆埃尔和卡瑟斯去哪儿了
So, Samuel and the Cuzzes?
不知道  他们匆匆离开了
Don't know. They left in a hurry.
我们在他们家那边汇合
I'm meeting them back at their place.
你  你要和我一起走吗
You, uh, you coming with me?
不
No.
我要回去照看莉莎和本
No, I'm going back for Lisa and Ben.
你说了...
I thought you said --
是的  我改变主意了
I did. I changed my mind.
听着  虽然我当时几乎是逼着你去找他们
Look, I practically shoved you at them.
这说法倒是挺好笑  继续
That's a funny way to put it, but all right.
我说的是  我也希望你能有个家
I'm just saying, I really wanted that for you.
我让你去找他们的时候  我是觉得
And when I told you to go, I-I thought...
你会幸福的
You could have it, you know?
但是现在我不确定了
But now I'm not so sure.
你需要考虑的实际情况是
I mean, you got to consider the fact
如果你回去了  会把他们推向火坑
that you'll be putting them in danger if you go back.
那该如何  最好远离他们么
So, what, it's better to leave them alone,
没人保护他们了
unprotected,
这样就没有危险了是么
and then they're not in danger?
这都是我一手造成的
I did this to them.
是我进入了他们的生活  他们才会有危险的
I made them vulnerable the moment I knocked on their door,
覆水难收  我无能为力
And I can't undo that.
但我能弥补的是  择优而行
But what I can do is go with the best option.
我明白了
I hear you.
我只是
I guess I just, uh
希望你能一起来  没别的
wish you were coming, that's all.
为什么
Why?
-别犯傻了  -不  我认真的
- Don't be stupid. - No, I mean it.
你认识那么多优秀的猎魔人
I mean, you know plenty of good hunters.
我都生疏了
I'm rusty.
我刚刚就那么冲过去  实在是极度愚蠢
I did something seriously stupid going out there.
差点连累我俩都死了
I almost got us both killed.
这就是为什么我需要你
And that's exactly why I want you.
你这是什么意思
What are you talking about?
你坚决果断
You just went.
毫不犹豫
You didn't hesitate.
因为你在乎他们  你就是这样的人
Because you care, and that's who you are.
我
Me?
我连去尝试的想法都没有
I wouldn't even think to try.
不  你也会那么做的
Yes, you would.
不  迪恩
No, Dean.
我要告诉你  有你在身边很好
I'm telling you, it's just better with you around.
就这样
That's all.
听着
Listen...
她应该继续猎魔的  带上她
She should be hunting. Take her.
谢谢  真的
Thanks. Really.
但我有一辆自己的爱车了
But I already got my car set up how I like it.
我该上路了
I should hit the road.
我送你出去
I'll walk you out.
保持联系  听到了吗
Keep in touch, you hear?
当然
'course.
能再见到你真不错  迪恩
It was really good to see you again, Dean.